he.net 2018-06-25

# Privacy Policy

**Hurricane Electric Privacy Policy**

Welcome to the Hurricane Electric Privacy Policy. Hurricane Electric is committed to protecting your privacy online. The following privacy policy explains what information we gather about you, and what it is used for. 

**Information**

When you place an order we need to know your name, email address, company name, postal address, phone number, and your payment information. We need this information to process your order and to contact you, should there be a problem with your order. 

**Use of information**

We do not disclose any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, postal address, email address or telephone number, to any third party except as necessary to register new domains as requested by you. We use the information that we collect to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; additionally, we use it to analyze site usage, and to improve our product offerings. 

We will use your email address and if need be your postal address or phone number to contact you regarding administrative issues, maintenance issues, and about any change in the function(s) of our services. 

We may also store the information that we gather from you in a file along with any email or other written correspondence that we have had with you. This information may be used to enforce our terms of service, or to resolve legal matters. 

**Cookies**

Upon entering Hurricane Electric's website, a cookie is created. The information that this cookie displays is where you came from. For example, if you found Hurricane Electric from a search engine, the cookie will tell us from which search engine. 

We use cookies to track where visitors are coming from. We look at which search engines, directories, and other web sites are bringing traffic to our site. 

**Disclosure**

Hurricane Electric will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process, or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. Hurricane Electric may disclose any information about their users under special circumstances that include but are not limited to complying with the law, or assisting in rectifying an unjust doing. 

**Passwords**

We strongly recommend that you limit access to your password(s) as much as possible. If possible do not disclose your password to anyone. Should someone with access to your password wish, all of your account information can be changed. You will be held liable for any activity that may occur as a result of you losing your password. Therefore, if you feel that your password has been compromised, you should immediately contact Hurricane Electric to rectify the situation.
